Guide to the Peter E. Palmquist Collection of Male Photographers in the American West
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographic Materials, circa 1840-2003; Series II; (231 boxes)
  - Photographic Materials
    - Rivers, Thomas L. (Box 488)
    - Riverside Studio (Box 488)
    - Robelet, M. C. (Box 488)
    - Roberts, B. L. (Box 488)
    - Roberts, H. F. (Box 488)
    - Roberts, Mike (Box 488)
    - Robinson and Crandall (Box 488)
    - Robinson and Weishar (Box 488)
    - Robinson, T. G. (Box 488)
    - Roche, Thomas C. (Box 488)
    - Rodolph, Frank B. (Box 488)
    - Roe, James (Box 488)
    - Roesch, Louis (Box 488)
    - Rogers & Rue (Box 488)
    - Rogers, Alfred Horace (Box 488)
    - Rogers, C. T. (Box 488)
    - Rogers, Fred H. (Box 488)
    - Rogers, R. (Box 488)
    - Roos & Wunderlich (Box 488)
    - Rose & Company (Box 488)
    - Rose, G. L., 2 (Box 488)
    - Ross & Ormsby (Box 489)
    - Ross & Piggott (Box 489)
    - Ross, George, 2 (Box 489)
    - Ross, John (Box 489)
    - Roussel and Palmer (Box 489)
    - Royal Photo Studio, 2 (Box 489)
    - Rubens (Box 489)
    - Rudd & Penny (Box 489)
    - Rue, L. M. (Box 489)
    - Rue, S. M. (Box 489)
    - Rule, Eugene L. (Box 489)
    - Rulofson and Hamlin (Box 489)
    - Rulofson, William Herman (Box 490)
    - Runnels & Company (Box 489)
    - Runnels & Stateler (Box 489)
    - Russell (Box 489)
    - Ruth, J. (Box 489)
    - Rutland, Fred (Box 489)
    - Ryder, Charles H. (Box 489)
    - Salb, Albert (Box 491)
    - Salmon, W. (Box 491)
    - Sammis, Edward M. (Box 491)
    - Samuel, Ford E. (Box 491)
    - Samuels and Forzani (Box 491)
    - Samuels, Michael A. (Box 491)
    - San Benito Gallery (Box 491)
    - San Francisco Art & Photographic Gallery (Box 491)
    - San Francisco Art Company (Box 491)
    - San Francisco Camera Exchange (Box 491)
    - San Francisco Institute of Art (Box 491)
    - San Francisco Photo Company (Box 491)
    - San Francisco Photo Engraving Company (Box 491)
    - San Francisco Salon (Box 491)
    - San Francisco Sunday Examiner (Box 491)
    - San Jose Camera Club (Box 491)
    - San Pablo Gallery (Box 491)
    - San Rafael Photograph Gallery (Box 491)
    - Sanders and Stinson (Box 491)
    - Sanders, Stephen Poole (Box 491)
    - Sanders, Wiltshire (Box 491)
    - Sarida, Joseph (Box 491)
    - Saunders, B. (Box 491)
    - Savage and Ottinger (Box 491)
    - Savage, John (Box 491)
    - Savoy Studio (Box 491)
    - Sawyer, J. W. (Box 491)
    - Scenic View Card Company (Box 491)
    - Schaffer, C. E. (Box 491)
    - Scharz, R. E. (Box 491)
    - Scheff, I. & Bros. (Box 491)
    - Schellenberg, M. O. (Box 491)
    - Scheuch (Box 491)
    - Schillcock, H. F. (Box 491)
    - Schlechten (Box 491)
    - Schmidt Label and Lithographic Company (Box 491)
    - Schmolz, William (Box 491)
    - Schneider & Simas (Box 491)
    - Schneider, Max (Box 491)
    - Schoene, H., 5 (Box 492)
    - Schofield Studio (Box 491)
    - Scholl, Amelian (Box 491)
    - Scholten, John A. (Box 491)
    - Schramm, Mathien (Box 492)
    - Schreiner & Haas (Box 493)
    - Schroder, Edward (Box 493)
    - Schubert, G. H. (Box 493)
    - Schuffler, Chas., 5 (Box 494)
    - Schumacher, F. G., 6 (Box 495)
    - Schumacher, Leo J. (Box 493)
    - Schuman & Bruner (Box 493)
    - Schuman, Carl (Box 493)
    - Schwab & Sherman (Box 493)
    - Schwabacher-Frey Stationery Company (Box 493)
    - Schweitzer, J. B. (Box 493)
    - Schwichtenberg (Box 493)
    - Scott & Kittles (Box 493)
    - Scott, Ferris H. (Box 493)
    - Scott, R. Vere (Box 493)
    - Scott, Winfield (Box 493)
    - Scripture, J. C. (Box 493)
    - Sears & Collins (Box 493)
    - Sears, Charles L. (Box 493)
    - Seibert, John A. (Box 493)
    - Selleck, Silas Wright, 5 (Box 496)
    - Selleck, William (Box 493)
    - Sellers, Charles (Box 493)
    - Sewell & Hucks (Box 493)
    - Sewell, Daniel, 7 (Box 497)
    - Sewell, Edward Newton (Box 493)
    - Shaff, Martin V. (Box 493)
    - Shaffer, C. E. (Box 493)
    - Shaffner, Chas. H. (Box 493)
    - Sharpe, William H., 2 (Box 498)
    - Shattuck, William (Box 499)
    - Shaw (Box 499)
    - Shaw & Johnson (Box 499)
    - Shaw & Shaw (Box 499)
    - Shaw, Seth Lewis (Box 499)
    - Shaw, William, 2 (Box 500)
    - Sheldon, D. (Box 499)
    - Shelton, C. A. (Box 499)
    - Shepherd, Lafayette (Box 499)
    - Sherriff Brothers' (Box 499)
    - Sherriff, John A. (Box 499)
    - Sherriff, Thomas B. (Box 499)
    - Sherrod Studio (Box 499)
    - Shew & Bradford (Box 499)
    - Shew, Jacob, 5 (Box 501)
    - Shew, Myron (Box 499)
    - Shew, William, 16 (Box 502)
    - Shew, William (Box 503)
    - Shillcock, H. J. (Box 499)
    - Shilling & Company (Box 499)
    - Shinkle, J. C., 3 (Box 499)
    - Shoob, Tom (Box 499)
    - Shook, F. (Box 499)
    - Shoot the Chute Tin Type Gallery (Box 499)
    - Shortridge, E. L. (Box 499)
    - Shubert, Joseph (Box 499)
    - Shuford (Box 499)
    - Shull & Meacham (Box 499)
    - Sierra Art & Engraving Company (Box 504)
    - Sierra Club (Box 504)
    - Silva, J. T. (Box 504)
    - Silver (Box 504)
    - Silver, Joseph, 2 (Box 504)
    - Silver, O. B. (Box 504)
    - Silvis, J. B. (Box 504)
    - Simas (Box 504)
    - Simon & Robinson (Box 504)
    - Sims, Walter (Box 504)
    - Siskiyou Portrait Studio, 6 (Box 505)
    - Sloan, S. S. (Box 506)
    - Slocum, John E. (Box 506)
    - Smaus, Louis (Box 506)
    - Smith, 2 (Box 506)
    - Smith & Dryer (Box 506)
    - Smith Bros. (Box 506)
    - Smith Studio (Box 506)
    - Smith, AL, 2 (Box 506)
    - Smith, Albert (Box 506)
    - Smith, Chatfield (Box 506)
    - Smith, Francis A. (Box 506)
    - Smith, G. S. (Box 506)
    - Smith, Gary D. (Box 506)
    - Smith, Henry P. (Box 506)
    - Smith, James G., 4 (Box 507)
    - Smith, Jason (Box 506)
    - Smith, Jerry R. (Box 506)
    - Smith, Walter J. (Box 506)
    - Smith's CA Photo Car (Box 506)
    - Snelling, E & N (Box 506)
    - Snow, H. L. (Box 506)
    - Snyder (Box 506)
    - Sohon, Gustavus (Box 506)
    - Sontag Drug Store (Box 506)
    - Sorocco, Frank (Box 506)
    - Souther, Joseph W. (Box 506)
    - Souvenir Gallery (Box 506)
    - Souvenir Publishing Company (Box 506)
    - Special View Company (Box 506)
    - Spencer, E. W. (Box 506)
    - Spencer, Stephen Allen (Box 506)
    - Splane, Charles W. (Box 508)
    - Splar & Akers (Box 508)
    - Spooner & Brownell (Box 508)
    - Spooner, John Pitcher, 10 (Box 509)
    - Sprague, L. A., 2 (Box 510)
    - St. Louis Art & Photo Gallery (Box 508)
    - Stagenwald, Hugo (Box 508)
    - Stanford Studio (Box 508)
    - Stanton & Burdick (Box 508)
    - Stanton, H. L. & Company (Box 508)
    - Stanton, M. C. (Box 508)
    - Stanton, Thomas Elwood (Box 508)
    - Staples, C. H. (Box 508)
    - Staples, H. A. (Box 508)
    - Stapleton, R. (Box 508)
    - Starbuck, Thomas (Box 508)
    - Stark (Box 508)
    - Starkweather, Joseph B. (Box 508)
    - Starlight Color Lab (Box 508)
    - Starr Galery (Box 508)
    - Stearns, S. S. (Box 508)
    - Steckel, George, 4 (Box 511)
    - Steiner Studio (Box 508)
    - Stellman, Louis J., 2 (Box 512)
    - Stemm, N. C. (Box 508)
    - Stenberg, Edward R. (Box 508)
    - Stender's Studio (Box 508)
    - Stengel, Robert H. (Box 508)
    - Stephens & Catherwood (Box 508)
    - Stevens, Albert B. (Box 508)
    - Stevens, L. (Box 508)
    - Stewart Photo Company (Box 508)
    - Stewart, George D., 2 (Box 508)
    - Stiffler, F. M. (Box 508)
    - Stimber, H. P. (Box 508)
    - Stinson, Lewis Jackson (Box 508)
    - Stinson, Robert E. (Box 508)
    - Stoddard & Porter (Box 508)
    - Storm, F. D. (Box 508)
    - Stormer & Nelson (Box 508)
    - Stormer, J. B. (Box 508)
    - Stratman, John (Box 508)
    - Strauss, B. R. (Box 513)
    - Street, William J. (Box 513)
    - Streeter, G. A. (Box 513)
    - Stringfield, A. M., 3 (Box 514)
    - Strong, Joseph Dwight Jr. (Box 513)
    - Strong, M. H., 4 (Box 515)
    - Strong, N. B. (Box 513)
    - Strong, R. W. (Box 513)
    - Strunz & Woodworth (Box 513)
    - Stuart, William McCorsion, 3 (Box 516)
    - Studio Grand (Box 513)
    - Stupacich Manufacturing Company (Box 513)
    - Sturges, Jock (Box 513)
    - Sturgess & Taylor (Box 513)
    - Styleman (Box 513)
    - Suden, F. G. (Box 513)
    - Suhr, Charles (Box 513)
    - Suits, G. W. & J. J. (Box 513)
    - Sullivan & Jenkins (Box 513)
    - Sullivan, Frank (Box 513)
    - Sun Drug Company (Box 513)
    - Sun Photo Service (Box 513)
    - Sunbeam Art Gallery, 3 (Box 517)
    - Sunbeam Gallery (Box 517)
    - Sunbeam Studio (Box 513)
    - Sunbeam Studio (Box 517)
    - Sunset Photo & Engraving Company (Box 513)
    - Sunset Photo Supply Company (Box 513)
    - Sunset Studio (Box 513)
    - Sutherland (Box 513)
    - Sutterley & Company (Box 518)
    - Sutterley & Dart (Box 518)
    - Sutterley & Noe (Box 518)
    - Sutterley & Rendall (Box 518)
    - Sutterley Bros., 2 (Box 518)
    - Sutterley, C., 2 (Box 518)
    - Swadley, W. W. (Box 513)
    - Swain & Simas (Box 513)
    - Swain, Francis C. (Box 513)
    - Swanander, P. (Box 513)
    - Swart, J. S., 5 (Box 519)
    - Swasey & Button (Box 513)
    - Swasey, Benjamin (Box 513)
    - T. C. W. Company (Box 520)
    - Taber Photo Company (Box 520)
    - Taber, Isaiah West, 21 (Box 521)
    - Taber, Isaiah West (Box 522)
    - Taber, Isaiah West (Box 523)
    - Tandy, H. C. (Box 520)
    - Taylor (Box 520)
    - Taylor, D. B. & Company (Box 520)
    - Taylor, Edward DeWitt (Box 520)
    - Taylor, Harold A. (Box 520)
    - Taylor, S. M. (Box 520)
    - Temple Block Gallery (Box 520)
    - Tent City Gallery (Box 520)
    - Terkelson & Henry, 2 (Box 520)
    - Ternberg Studio (Box 520)
    - Tesio, George A., 2 (Box 520)
    - Thomas, G. N. (Box 520)
    - Thompson (Box 520)
    - Thompson (Box 520)
    - Thompson (Box 520)
    - Thompson, Dr. (Box 520)
    - Thompson, Harry (Box 520)
    - Thornbrough, George W. (Box 520)
    - Thors, Louis, 6 (Box 524)
    - Thurston, W. C. (Box 520)
    - Thwaites, Joseph (Box 520)
    - Tibbits, Howard Clinton (Box 525)
    - Tieman, Charles H. (Box 525)
    - Todd, John A., 5 (Box 526)
    - Toenjes, D. G. (Box 525)
    - Tollman, J. W. (Box 525)
    - Tong & Appleton (Box 525)
    - Tong, John Hicks (Box 525)
    - Tonge, John H. (Box 525)
    - Tonkin, Herbert (Box 525)
    - Towers Company (Box 525)
    - Towne, B. C. (Box 525)
    - Towne, William Henry (Box 525)
    - Townsend & Son (Box 525)
    - Train & Cromwell (Box 525)
    - Train, Edgar Horace (Box 525)
    - Treat, Archibald Jennings (Box 525)
    - Tresslar & Gifford (Box 525)
    - Tresslar & Hays (Box 525)
    - Tresslar, Sidney Pinney (Box 525)
    - Tripp, J. W. (Box 525)
    - Tucker, J. O., 2 (Box 525)
    - Tullis, A. T. (Box 525)
    - Tully, C. H. (Box 525)
    - Turk Street Gallery (Box 525)
    - Turner & Judd (Box 527)
    - Turner, A. M. (Box 527)
    - Turner, Winslow E., 3 (Box 528)
    - Turney, J. H. (Box 527)
    - Turrill & Miller (Box 527)
    - Turrill, Charles Beebe (Box 527)
    - Tuttle & Benedict (Box 527)
    - Tuttle & Brownell (Box 527)
    - Tuttle & Fitzgerald (Box 527)
    - Tuttle & Johnson (Box 527)
    - Tuttle & Lee (Box 527)
    - Tuttle & Park (Box 527)
    - Tuttle, Burt H. (Box 527)
    - Tuttle, Charles K. (Box 527)
    - Tuttle, William Nutting, 4 (Box 527)
    - Twining H. N. (Box 527)
    - Tyler, O. E. (Box 527)
    - Tyler, W. B. (Box 527)
    - Uberto, Cesare (Box 529)
    - Uchiyama (Box 529)
    - Underwood & Underwood (Box 529)
    - Union Photo Engraving Company (Box 529)
    - Unique Studio (Box 529)
    - Universal Art Studio (Box 529)
    - Universal Photo Art Company (Box 529)
    - Vale, W. A. (Box 529)
    - Valenta, Jerry (Box 529)
    - Valentine & Darlington (Box 529)
    - Valentine, W. S. (Box 529)
    - Valleau, George W. (Box 529)
    - Vallejo Art Gallery (Box 529)
    - Van Buskirk, Charles (Box 529)
    - Van Court, James Edward, 2 (Box 529)
    - Van Der Kaaij, William J. (Box 529)
    - Van Diver, William J., 2 (Box 529)
    - Van E___ (Box 529)
    - Van Ornum, Drake, & Melville (Box 529)
    - Vance, Robert H., 38 (Box 530)
    - Vance, Robert H. (Box 531)
    - Vandiveer & Porter (Box 529)
    - Vanity Fair Studios (Box 529)
    - Van's Gallery, 2 (Box 529)
    - Van's Studio (Box 529)
    - Vansant, Joshua, Sr. (Box 529)
    - Varney, Augustus K. (Box 529)
    - Vasser (Box 529)
    - Vaughan & Keith (Box 529)
    - Vaughan, Hiram G., 5 (Box 532)
    - Venturanza (Box 529)
    - Ver Halen Publishing Company (Box 529)
    - Vert Inc. Camera Stores (Box 529)
    - Viales B Studio (Box 529)
    - Vingrad, Nicholas (Box 529)
    - Vitalini, C. E. (Box 529)
    - Vogue Drug Company (Box 529)
    - Volmer & Lowry (Box 529)
    - Von Oorschot, Henry (Box 529)
    - Vreeland (Box 529)
    - Vroman, Adam Clark (Box 529)
    - Wagar Photo (Box 533)
    - Waite, 2 (Box 533)
    - Waite, C. B. (Box 533)
    - Wakefield, Leland Howard (Box 533)
    - Wakelee's Pharmacies (Box 533)
    - Wakely, George D. (Box 533)
    - Walker (Box 533)
    - Walker, Carolus Malcolm (Box 533)
    - Wallace, Hugh (Box 533)
    - Wallace-Zorn (Box 533)
    - Walter & Hemenway (Box 533)
    - Walters & Company (Box 533)
    - Walz & Lare (Box 533)
    - Ward (Box 533)
    - Ward, Edward (Box 533)
    - Warren, William E. (Box 533)
    - Washburn, C. H. (Box 533)
    - Waterhouse & Butler (Box 533)
    - Watkins, Carleton E., 665 (Box 534)
    - Watkins, Carleton E. (Box 535)
    - Watkins, Carleton E. (Box 536)
    - Watkins, Carleton E. (Box 537)
    - Watrous, S. W. (Box 533)
    - Watson, A. R. (Box 533)
    - Watson, W. (Box 533)
    - Webb, George (Box 538)
    - Weber, H. (Box 538)
    - Webster & Albee (Box 538)
    - Webster Bros. (Box 538)
    - Webster, Benton (Box 538)
    - Webster, Frederick Arthur, 6 (Box 539)
    - Webster's New Studio (Box 538)
    - Weed, Chester L., 16 (Box 540)
    - Weidner, Charles (Box 538)
    - Weinstock, Lubin & Company (Box 538)
    - Weishar, 2 (Box 538)
    - Weitz & Dijeau (Box 538)
    - Weitz, Hugo, 2 (Box 538)
    - Welch, J. A. (Box 538)
    - Weller, L. A. (Box 538)
    - Wells & Denning (Box 538)
    - Wells & Inch (Box 538)
    - Wells, T. O., 42 (Box 541)
    - Wells, T. O. (Box 542)
    - Welsh, J. O. (Box 538)
    - Werner (Box 538)
    - Wertz (Box 538)
    - Wertz, George (Box 538)
    - Wertz, J. C. (Box 538)
    - Wesner, M. A., 2 (Box 538)
    - West Union Photo Company (Box 543)
    - Western Photo Company (Box 543)
    - Western Publishing & Novelty Company, 2 (Box 543)
    - Westervelt & Coules (Box 543)
    - Westervelt, J. D. (Box 543)
    - Westfall (Box 543)
    - Weston (Box 543)
    - Weston, Edward (Box 543)
    - Weston, H. (Box 543)
    - Weyle & Sprague (Box 543)
    - Weyle, E. (Box 543)
    - Whigham, R. P., 3 (Box 544)
    - Whisler's Iowa Photo Studio (Box 543)
    - White, George R. (Box 543)
    - Whitney, E. L. (Box 543)
    - Whitney, Frank L. (Box 543)
    - Whitney's Movie Photos (Box 543)
    - Whitten, C. H. (Box 543)
    - Whittington, Dick (Box 543)
    - Wilbur (Box 543)
    - Wilcox (Box 543)
    - Wilkins, Ira (Box 543)
    - Willard, S. L. (Box 543)
    - Williams & McDonald (Box 545)
    - Williams & Norton (Box 545)
    - Williams & Samuels (Box 545)
    - Williams, B. S. (Box 545)
    - Williams, Edward A. (Box 545)
    - Williams, George L. (Box 545)
    - Williams, H. E. (Box 545)
    - Williams, J. (Box 545)
    - Williams, J. C. (Box 545)
    - Williams, W. I. (Box 545)
    - Willis & Hamilton (Box 545)
    - Willis Photo Lab (Box 545)
    - Wilson, C. T. (Box 545)
    - Wilson, Charles W. (Box 545)
    - Wilson's California Photo Tent (Box 545)
    - Wilton, C. H. (Box 545)
    - Winberg, J. A. (Box 545)
    - Wing & Allen (Box 545)
    - Wing & Chandler (Box 545)
    - Winstead Bros. (Box 545)
    - Winter & Funston (Box 545)
    - Winter & Pond (Box 545)
    - Winter, J. A. (Box 545)
    - Winter, William (Box 545)
    - Wise & Prindle (Box 545)
    - Wiskotschill, I. N. (Box 545)
    - Witzel (Box 545)
    - Wohleb, H. (Box 546)
    - Wolfe & Kildare (Box 546)
    - Wolfe & Recht (Box 546)
    - Wolfe, S. A. (Box 546)
    - Wolfenstein, V. (Box 546)
    - Wonnacott, H. H., 2 (Box 547)
    - Wood (Box 546)
    - Wood, Albert W. (Box 546)
    - Wood, R. E. (Box 546)
    - Wood, T. M. (Box 546)
    - Woods & Michaels (Box 546)
    - Woods & Thompson (Box 546)
    - Woods' Gallery (Box 546)
    - Wood's Studio (Box 546)
    - Woods, A. (Box 546)
    - Woods, D. H., 2 (Box 546)
    - Woods, George R. (Box 546)
    - Woolsey, E. (Box 546)
    - Worden, Willard E., 2 (Box 548)
    - Worthington, W. T. (Box 546)
    - Wright, E. G. (Box 546)
    - Wright, W. W., 5 (Box 549)
    - Wright, William B. (Box 546)
    - Wyllie, E. A. S. (Box 546)
    - Wyman, F. O. (Box 546)
    - Yale, W. A. (Box 550)
    - Yeager, F. V. (Box 550)
    - Yong, Lai (Box 550)
    - Yosemite Engraving Company (Box 550)
    - Young, Conrad (Box 550)
    - Zan (Box 550)
    - Zimmerman, Charles A. (Box 550)
    - Zink, J. F. (Box 550)
    - Zuber, William L. (Box 550)
    - Zwarg (Box 550)
    - Zykkian Studio (Box 550)
  - Oversize Photographic Materials
    This subseries consists of photographic materials created by or documenting individual photographers. It includes vintage photographic prints and copy photographs created by Palmquist, as well as some associated publications, tear sheets, and ephemera that possess dimensions greater than 22 x 29 centimeters (8.7 x 11.4 inches).
    - Abell, George (Box 551 (Oversize))
    - Adams, Ansel (Box 551 (Oversize))
    - Alt, Rudolph (Box 551 (Oversize))
    - Austin Studios (Box 551 (Oversize))
    - Barry (Box 551 (Oversize))
    - Bast, W. (Box 552 (Oversize))
    - Berry & Sinclair (Box 551 (Oversize))
    - Blake Studios (Box 551 (Oversize))
    - Boussum, Charles (Box 551 (Oversize))
    - Boyé, Otto H. (Box 551 (Oversize))
    - Bradley & Rulofson (Box 551 (Oversize))
    - Bradley & Rulofson, Composite photograph of the graduates of the Hasting's College of Law in San Francisco, California, 1884 (Box 553 (Broadside))
    - Britt, Peter, 2 (Box 551 (Oversize))
    - Bruguiere, P. S. (Box 551 (Oversize))
    - Bushnell, Fred H., 2 (Box 554 (Oversize))
    - Cook, Geoff (Box 554 (Oversize))
    - Cromwell, Oscar (Box 554 (Oversize))
    - Curtis, Charles (Box 554 (Oversize))
    - Curtis, Edward S., 2 (Box 554 (Oversize))
    - Dames & Hayes (Box 555 (Oversize))
    - Davidson (Box 555 (Oversize))
    - De Monbrun (Box 555 (Oversize))
    - Doré Studio (Box 555 (Oversize))
    - Eastern Art Company (Box 555 (Oversize))
    - Eastern Studio (Box 555 (Oversize))
    - Edouart (Box 555 (Oversize))
    - Elite (Box 555 (Oversize))
    - Franklin, J. C. (Box 555 (Oversize))
    - Fullertore (Box 555 (Oversize))
    - Gainsborough (Box 555 (Oversize))
    - Genthe, Arnold (Box 555 (Oversize))
    - Giannini (Box 555 (Oversize))
    - Goldbeck, Eugene Omar (Box 555 (Oversize))
    - Hammond's Studio (Box 555 (Oversize))
    - Hart, A. A. (Box 555 (Oversize))
    - Hartsook, Fred J. (Box 555 (Oversize))
    - Haussler, F. O. (Box 555 (Oversize))
    - Heller, Louis Herman (Box 555 (Oversize))
    - Hill, Andrew Putnam (Box 555 (Oversize))
    - Hirsch & Kaiser (Box 555 (Oversize))
    - Hodson, Burton M. (Box 556 (Oversize))
    - Houseworth, William (Box 556 (Oversize))
    - Jackson, William Henry (Box 556 (Oversize))
    - James Studio (Box 556 (Oversize))
    - Johnson, A. J., 3 (Box 556 (Oversize))
    - Johnson, Albert, Composite photograph of infants, 1922; 2 photographic prints (Box 557 (Broadside))
    - Johnson, Charles Wallace Jacob (Box 556 (Oversize))
    - Jones, John Wesley (Box 556 (Oversize))
    - Lawrence, George R. (Box 556 (Oversize))
    - Liebart, Alphonse (Box 556 (Oversize))
    - Marceau, Theodore C., 2 (Box 556 (Oversize))
    - Maxwell and Mudge (Box 556 (Oversize))
    - McLeod, Norman (Box 556 (Oversize))
    - McMillan Bros. (Box 556 (Oversize))
    - Mission Art Company (Box 556 (Oversize))
    - Mitchell (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Moore, Aurthur R. (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Morell, James (Box 559 (Oversize))
    - Moulin, Gabriel (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Muybridge, Eadweard J. (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Novak (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Novak & Coleman (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Palmquist and Jurgens (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Peterson, Edward H. (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Pillsbury Photo Picture Company (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Putnam & Valentine (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Ravnos, Ole (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Rea, Thomas L. (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Reilly, John James, Members of the Marysville Society of California pioneers, circa 1878 (Box 560 (Broadside))
    - Rorelli, Anthony (Box 559 (Oversize))
    - Savage, Charles R. (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Savard, Alphonse (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Scholl and Kleckner (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Selleck, Silas Wright (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Sherer (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Shew, Myron (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Shew, William (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Shigetomi, A. (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Slocum, John E. (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Southwest Studio (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Spooner, John Pitcher, 2 (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Spuri Studio (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - St. Francis Studio (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Steiner Studio (Box 558 (Oversize))
    - Sunset Studio (Box 561 (Oversize))
    - Taber, Isaiah West (Box 561 (Oversize))
    - Terkelson & Henry (Box 561 (Oversize))
    - Tilston-Jones, H. (Box 561 (Oversize))
    - Tucker, J. O. (Box 561 (Oversize))
    - Valentine (Box 561 (Oversize))
    - Vance, Robert H. (Box 561 (Oversize))
    - Vincent, Fred E. (Box 561 (Oversize))
    - Vischer, Edward (Box 561 (Oversize))
    - Walters, R. J. (Box 561 (Oversize))
    - Watkins, Carleton E., 2 (Box 562 (Oversize))
    - Wayne (Box 561 (Oversize))
    - Weber, H. (Box 561 (Oversize))
    - Webster, Frederick Arthur (Box 561 (Oversize))
    - Weed, Charles L. (Box 561 (Oversize))
    - Weidner, Charles (Box 561 (Oversize))
    - Willis & Hamilton (Box 561 (Oversize))
    - Worden, Willard E. (Box 561 (Oversize))
    - Zante, A. (Box 561 (Oversize))
    - Zink, J. F. (Box 561 (Oversize))
  - Photograph Albums
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by the surname of the photographer, the corporate name of the studio, or name of the compiler.
    This subseries consists of photograph albums and scrapbooks of various sizes created by photographers and compilers.
    - Brown, Arthur Merrill, Jr., 1925 (Box 563)
      Related Archival Materials note
      His wife also created photograph albums. See: Peter Palmquist collection of Women in Photography (WA MSS S-2600), Series II. Photographic Materials Photograph Albums, Brown, Arthur Merrill, Mrs, Boxes 338-340.
      Photograph album documenting a trip to China
    - Crouch, Steve, 1959 October 5 (Box 564)
      Photograph album documenting the Wedding of Faye Mendelsohn and Daniel Roy Haskins
    - Eberspacher, William, circa 1910 (Box 565)
      Photograph album of studio portraits of men and women, probably high school students in Holdrege, Nebraska
    - Fitch, Walter T., 1894-1910 (Box 566)
      Photograph album that documents timber harvesting related to coast redwood trees and the Union Lumber Company in Fort Bragg, California
    - Hecht, True E., circa 1910 (Box 567)
      Disbound photograph album of copy photographs of images that document San Francisco, California, circa 1856-1905
    - Herold, Edward, circa 1932; 2 photograph albums (Box 568, Box 568a)
      Photograph albums documenting military service with the 31st Infantry Regiment of the United States Army in the Philippine Islands
    - Walther, Benjamin, and Mary B. Walther, 1935 (Box 569)
      Photograph album documenting a trip to Brazil
    - Unidentified Photographers and Compilers